bloggertheme9.com 2016-06-23

# Privacy Policy Blogger Template | Bloggertheme9

At **Bloggertheme9.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by bloggertheme9.com and how it is used. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Bloggertheme9.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Bloggertheme9.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

**Contact Information**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.bloggertheme9.com/p/contact.html).
